>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 作为我们的基金会，那些抽象的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: With those as our
foundation, those abstract operations as
我们的基础现在是我们切换齿轮，真正的威逼话题的时候了。
our foundation it is now time for us to
switch gears and really topic of coercion.
就像我在外面说的一样这需要
And by the way as I said at the out set,
this is going to require for
你能从我的计划中得到任何东西
you to get anything out of what I'm about
to say over this next bit it's gonna
要求你敞开心心
require you to have an open mind.
因为你被安排好相信这是一个邪恶的模糊
Because you have been so programmed
to believe that this is an evil buggy
你应该避免的 JavaScript 的可怕部分
horrible part of JavaScript
that you should avoid,
很难看到这个讨论的价值和价值
that it's hard to see any value or
merit out of this discussion.
但我把它放在了这个课程的顶端
But I make it such a point of put
it in the very top of this course
因为我觉得它是最受重视的
because I think it's one of
the most under valued and
在所有 JavaScript中都是这样
under looked that things
in all of JavaScript.
首先我知道你们大多数人都遵循这一行为
So to start off with I know most
of you follow that behavior and
这条建议说不我只是躲避强迫人
that advice that says,
no I just avoid coercions.
我用的是三等，我不处理类型，不是那么多。
I just use the triple equals,
I don't deal with types, not so much.
我们来看一些已经在进行胁迫的例子
Let's look at some examples where
you're already doing coercion
不管你意识到与否
whether you realize it or not.
您几年前是否使用了 ES6 ( 模板字面值字符串) ?
Any of you use the ES6 as of a few years
ago, the template-literal strings?
嗯。 我一定要把这些都用在这里
Yeah.
I certainly use these all over the place.
这是一种缓慢燃烧的过程。
This is one of those slow burns.
当我第一次出来的时候，我不太关心这个功能，
Cuz when it first came out, I didn't
really care about this feature, and
现在我喜欢这个功能
now I love this feature.
可能是我最喜欢的三种特色
Might be on my top three
favorite features.
我一直使用它，尤其是在 colsole.log 语句中。
I use it all the time,
especially in my colsole.log statements.
我到处都是用它我喜欢模板线
I just use it everywhere and
I love template strings.
如果你把值放到这些表情里
And if you drop in values
into those expressions,
可能和你们所有人都一样
that aren't already strings,
probably, like all of you.
猜猜发生了什么
Guess, what's happening there?
那个号码是暗指邪恶的
That number is getting coers to a string,
implicitly, evil,
你已经在做强逼的事了
you're already doing coercion,
all of you, period.
不管道格 - 克劳福说过什么你都在胁迫我
No matter what Doug Crawford said,
you're doing coercion,
你依赖的是你的计划中的胁迫
you're relying upon
coercion in your programs.
这并不是一件坏事，这是一件非常好的事情。
And that's not a bad thing,
that's a perfectly great thing.
但在封面下你应该有一个心理模型
But under the covers, you should have
the mental model that what's happening
我要带一个字符串， msg1 ，并将它添加到数字中。
here is I'm taking a string,
msg1, and adding it to a number.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在，为什么最终会产生一种胁迫呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now,
why is that end up producing a coercion?
其实是在调用另一个小魔法
Well, it's actually invoking
another a little magical
程序员喜欢做的事情就是我们的操作员过载了
thing that programmers love to do which
is we've got operator overloading.
通常认为加号运算符正在进行数字操作。
The plus operator is normally thought
of is doing numerical operation.
我的意思是 ...
Thought?
这个规范说如果你用一个字符串加上一个加运算符
The spec says that if you use the plus
operator with something that's a string,
这里有很多你可能做过的例子
and here's an example that lot
of you have probably done.
将空字符串添加到要将其转换为数字的字符串。
Add an empty string to a thing
to turn it into a number.
你有没有停下来想过这有多好
Did you ever stop to
wonder how that worked?
因为幽灵说那个加操作工
Well, it's because the specs
says that the plus operator.
如果其中一个是字符串，请注意，如果其中一个是字符串，那么通知
If either one of them is a string, notice
that or there, if either one of them is
字符串，加号运算符更喜欢字符串并置。
a string, the plus operator
prefers string concatenation.
>> Kyle Simpson: 这意味着，如果其中一个是字符串，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Which means,
if only one of them is a string,
你猜另一个会怎么样
guess what's gonna
happen to the other one?
一个两弦的手术在 7.a
A two-string operation right there on 7.a.
它会对它发出两串抽象的运算
It's gonna call a two string
abstract operation on it, and
把它变成一个绳子上面有所有怪胎
turn it in to a string with all of
the weirdnesses in caveats there of.
当它是一个很有格式的数字，就像号码 16 ，没有这么大的交易。
When it's a well formed number,
like the number 16, not such a big deal.
但有很多关于数字的转角处
But there's lots of corner
cases on numbers, and
很多街角的案例都是关于其他价值的，你只是很高兴地调用这些东西
lots of corner cases on other values, and
you're just invoking these things happily,
一点都不担心你在用高压手段
and not worrying at all,
about the fact that you're using coercion.
不我不是来告诉你不要用胁迫我是来告诉你的
No, I'm not here to tell you to stop
using coercion, I'm here to tell you
你用的是威逼，所以你就不明白了吗 ?
you're using coercion, so wouldn't
it make sense for you to learn it?
这就是我们潜入的原因好吗
That's why we dive into this, okay?
所以你可以说听我说我不喜欢那些含蓄的强迫
So, you may say, well, listen, I don't
like to do those implicit coercions,
我想做个非常明确的事
I wanna be super explicit about it.
好吧有一些疯狂的方式你可以明确的说
Okay, so, here's some crazy ways
that you can be explicit about it,
我那天才学会的
I just learned this one the other day.
我甚至都没考虑过你能把值扔进数组里
I never even considered that you
could throw a value into an array,
将一个值正好放入一个数组，然后调用点连接。
just the one value into an array,
and then call dot join on it.
即使它没有字符串并置，它也会在
And that actually ends up string it even
though it does no string concatenation at
全部，该连接的规范首先将其转换为字符串。
all, the spec for
that join first turns it into a string.
别这么做太糟糕了但如果你想做超级清晰的
Don't do this that's a terrible idea, but
you could if you wanna be super explicit
你可以说我只是在这里做字符串连接
about, you could say listen,
I'm only doing string concatenations here.
所以我要把我的号码变成一个字符串
So I'm gonna be explicit about
turning my number into a string.
还有一些其他的可能更完善的
Here's some other ones that
are maybe a little more well formed.
例如，您可以调用 toString 方法。
You might, for example,
call the toString method.
好吧至少标签上的 toString 方法上面写着它在做什么
Okay, cool, the toString method at least
on the label says what it's doing.
它会把一个数字变成一个字符串，这样就不会太坏了。
It's gonna turn a number into a string so
that's not too bad.
这里有点怪异你是怎么说的
There's a little weirdness here which
is how are you calling a method on
原始值吗 ?
a primitive value?
原语值没有方法。
Primitive values don't have methods.
所以你其实已经在这里做隐含的胁迫
So you're actually already still
doing implicit coercion here and
我们会回来的
we'll come back to that.
如果你不想做任何暗示的话
If you don't wanna do any
implicit coercion at all,
基本上是你唯一的选择
basically your only option.
要使用该基本对象而不使用新的关键字字符串，
Is to use that fundamental object
without a new keyword string,
这就是我把这个号码明确地强制给一个字符串的首选方法，
and this is my preferred way of explicitly
coercing that number to a string,
资本 S 弦函数会为你做的
the capital S string function
is gonna do that for you.
所以，如果你是其中一个说话的人，听着，所有的那些含蓄的东西，
So, if you're one of those that says hey,
listen, all those implicit things,
这些都是神奇的我们不想做
those are magical and
we don't wanna do them, and
你想清楚它的存在有一个明显的例子
you wanna be explicit about it, there's
an example of being explicit about it.
我不太确定那是个好主意
I'm not so sure that that's a great idea
但这至少是一种明确的方式
in all cases, but
that's at least a way of being explicit.
好了好了好了好了好了好了好了好了
All right, all right, all right, so
string to, number to string all right, but
还有别的办法吗
what about the other way around?
你也已经这样做了
[LAUGH] You're already doing that too.
因为你们都在处理 Web 应用程序，或者
Because all of you are dealing
with web applications, or
至少大多数人都在处理网络应用
at least most of you are dealing
with web applications which means
您正在处理用户输入的内容，如表单元素。
you're dealing with user input
from things like form elements.
这意味着你把东西当绳子
Which means you're grabbing
things as strings, and
那你就跟他们一起做数字
then you're just doing
numeric stuff with them.
当你把那个字符串值扔在加号操作上就像我在这儿
When you throw that string value at
the plus operation, like I'm doing here,
你猜会发生什么
guess what happens?
我们有一个字符串连接
Oops, we get a string concatenation.
而不是在 17岁的情况下，我们得到了字符串 161。
Instead of getting 17,
we get the string 161.
好吧好吧我先把它逼成一个数字
But okay, okay, I'll go ahead and
force it to be a number.
好的，有两种方法可以迫使它成为第一种，这加上了这里的运营商。
Okay, there's two ways of forcing it to
be a number one, this plus operator here.
一元加运算符 ( 如果您将在该规范中查找 ) 。
The unary plus operator,
if you'll look in the spec for it.
猜猜我们预料到什么抽象行动
Guess what it invokes which abstract
operation when we expect that turns out
两个数字的抽象化操作
that the two number abstract operation,
okay?
只是确定你都是这样好吗
Just making sure you're all the way, okay?
它调用这两个数字操作，即它所做的所有操作。
It invokes the two number operation,
that's all it does.
所以我们说的是把那东西作为一个字符串或者它是什么
So here we're saying take that thing
that's a string or whatever it is, and
在我们通过之前把它变成一个数字
turn it into a number
before we pass it in.
如果是字符串格式的格式正确的数字表示，那么
If it's a well-formed numeric
representation in string form, for
举个例子，你会在这里得到良好的结果，就像 17岁。
example, you're gonna end up
with good results here, like 17.
如果是空的你猜你要怎么做
If it's empty,
guess what you're gonna end up with?
>> Kyle Simpson: 空字符串会变成什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What's
the empty string gonna become?
零，它可能不是你想要的，但它会发生。
Zero, it may not be what you want but
it's gonna happen.
这里还有一个例子，这种胁迫发生在整个地方。
So here's another example this kind of
coercion happens all over the place.
我最大的挫折感是人们不去处理它然后就
And my biggest frustration is that people
don't deal with it and then just sort of
打个名号就是我不用担心的类型和胁迫。
slap a name badge on this is all I don't
have to worry about types and coercion.
我很擅长这就是虫子来自的地方
I'm good it's this,
this is where bugs come from.
使用您不了解其工作方式的工具。
Using tools that you don't
understand how they work.
好吧让我更具体说明一下即使在加士
Okay, so let me be more specific about it,
even in the plus operator,
也许看起来有点怪异
cuz it might look a little weird.
您可以使用基本号码功能，好的。
You can use the fundamental
number function, okay.
这是我的首选方法。
This is my preferred way.
如果我要把事情变成数字我就用数字功能
If I'm gonna turn something into a number,
I use the number function.
我们没有两个数字，所以这基本上是最语义的讲法
We don't have a two number, so this is
basically the most semantic way of telling
代码的读者会做出一些事情
the reader of code that you're gonna
make a number out of something.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果您使用减号运算符，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you use
a minus operator for example,
如果你和我有任何的嘲弄我就会把你踢出来
if any of you get too sarcastic
with me I'm gonna kick you up.
如果使用负运算符，那么仅为数字定义一个运算符。
If you use the minus operator that
one is only defined for numbers.
这不是超载的
That it's not overloaded for
字符串，从另一个字符串中减去一个字符串是没有意义的。
string, it wouldn't make any sense
to subtract one string from another.
那上面的负运算符会做什么
So that minus operator up there,
is gonna do what?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 来吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Come on?
两个号码好吗
Two number, okay?
它会调用这两个数字抽象操作。
It's gonna invoke that two
number abstract operation.
这些都是在您的程序中以各种不同的方式发生的事情。
These are all things that are happening in
your programs in various different ways.
我觉得把这些事情都说出来是个好主意
And I think it would be a good idea for
us to call these things out and
对它的认知有更多的了解
be a lot more aware of incognito
of it intentionally about.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，好的，字符串和数字都是工作的，但是你
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, okay, okay, strings
and numbers are always work things but you
知道我从来没做过什么因为我从没用过自己的布尔权来捣乱
know what I never do, because I never mess
around with coercion my Boolean, right?
如果在类中使用非 Booleans 的语句，那么我从不写。
Cuz I never write if statements that
use non-Booleans in the if class.
您是否使用任何类似检查来查看字符串是否为非空
Any of you use like checking to
see if a string is non-empty
看看这到底是真的吗
to see whether it's truthy or not?
非常普遍的做法，猜测所谓的胁迫。
Extremely common practice,
guess what that's called coercion.
好吧猜猜是什么
Okay, and guess what?
所有的奇怪的角落都是 Booleans 胁迫的案例
All of the weird corner cases of
coercion Booleans are in a fact,
即使你简单的说明他们是在一个事实中
even with your little simple if
statements they're in a fact.
事实上我要说有更多的例子是有布尔值的
Matter of fact, I would say there
are more corner cases with boolean,
可能比其他任何类型的总理
maybe than any other premier of type or
我们会在这个空虚的字符串里找到各种弱点
kinds of wearnesses that we're gonna get
into here as we go So that empty string,
如果学生把这个价值当作是虚无虚名的
if students input that value as an empty
that's gonna be falsy, alright?
但如果那串只是一堆白色的空间呢 ?
But what if that string has just
a bunch of white space in it?
现在它会是真实的对吧
Now it's gonna be truthy, right?
这不是你在乎的有效的字符串
It's not a valid string
that you care about because
它有一堆白色的地方但是突然它会变得更真实
it's got a bunch of white space in it but
all of a sudden it's going to be truthy.
甚至连我们的布尔都有
Corner cases even with our Boolean.
另一个喜欢的人喜欢用数字的数字胁迫
Another favorite one, people love to
use the numeric coercion of a number
要么是零钱要么不给零钱，对吧 ?
to either a zero or a non zero for
truthy or falsy, right?
所以如果我的长度是零就变成了假的
So if my length is zero
then it becomes false and
如果我的长度是非零值，那么它将变为 true。
if my length is anything non
zero then it becomes true.
因为它不是零，所以要依赖它。
Because it's not one of the zeros,
will have to rely up on that.
除非是 NaN
Except what happens when it's NaN.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好吧，所有这些要挟都有各种各样的例子。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, there's all kinds
of corner cases in all of these coercions.
所以如果你习惯使用其中一些
So if you're in the habit
of using some of these and
不是用别人的，我是说我不喜欢这样说，但是有点虚伪
not using others, I mean I hate to call
this out but it sort of hypocritical
说，我用这种形式或者魔术，但是我不喜欢这种形式的魔术。
to say, I used this form or magic but
I don't like that form of magic.
我不知道我们是否应该用魔法
I don't know if we should
use the magic at all,
我觉得我们应该学它，用它，然后它就不神奇了。
I think we should learn it, use it,
and then it's not magical at all.
一旦你知道了你是故意的
Once you learn it,
you're doing something intentional,
你把你的意图传达给其他人
and you're communicating
your intent to other people.
这并不意味着暗示总是坏事。
That does not mean that
implicitness is always bad.
事实上，牵连是很有用的。
As a matter of fact,
implicitness can be very useful.
这只是说，我们必须非常小心和有意。
It just simply means we have to
be very careful and intentional.
所以你可以说我喜欢把我所有的都变成露头的
So you might say well I like to turn
all of mine into explicit booleans.
所以你可以用这个
So you might use that.
在第一条线上翻两手
Double negate up there on line one.
Tha告诉它，变成一个布尔值。
Tha's telling it, become a boolean.
我在这张幻灯片上没有
I don't have it on this slide, but
您也可以使用基本资本 B 布尔值。
you could also use the fundamental
capital B Boolean.
这就是我想做的
That's what I prefer to do.
就像偏离了号码一样，我更喜欢使用大写 B 布尔。
Just like straying a number,
I prefer to use capital B Boolean.
但随着数字的增加而不是依靠数字的胁迫
But with numbers, it's better instead
of relying upon that numeric coercion,
用大于零的东西如果你是这个意思的话
use something like greater than zero,
if that's what you mean.
它不仅能保护你不受某些角落的影响
Not only does it protect you from some
of those corner cases, not all but some.
它保护您免受某些角落案例的影响，但它也更有语义。
It protects you from some of those corner
cases but it is also more semantic.
因为你在这里说，保持循环，长度大于零，
Because you are saying here, keep looping
while the length is greater than zero,
而不是保持循环而长度才是真实的
instead of keep looping
while the length is truthy.
这到底是什么意思
What does that even mean?
所以别用聪明的人来救几个字
So don't be clever just to
save a couple of characters,
在更能沟通的地方就更明确了。
be more explicit about it in the places
where explicitness is more communicative.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们已经讨论过其中的一些问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We already
covered some of this.
我在幻灯片里跳了下去。
I jumped ahead in my slides.
但是，空字符串的布尔值为 false。
But the Boolean of
an empty string is false.
非空字符串的布尔值为 true，这肯定是 gotcha。
The Boolean of a non-empty string is true,
and that's certainly gonna be a gotcha.
>> Kyle Simpson: 好的，布尔测试未定义且为空，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay,
the Boolean tests for undefined and null,
我们知道这两个人都在名单上
we know that both of
those are on the list.
我喜欢将空值和未定义的值视为不可区分的值。
I like to treat null and
undefined as indistinguishable values.
只要有可能
Wherever possible.
人们并不总是可以将它们区分为不可区分的。
It's not always possible to
treat them as indistinguishable.
但在可能的情况下我喜欢这样做
But where possible, I like to do so, and
凝聚力其实是很有帮助的。
cohesion actually is very helpful for
that.
但既然我们知道他们俩都是伪善人
But with respect to Boolean since we know
that they're both forcy, if the test that
我们要求的是这件事我们经常做
we're asking for is has this thing
been set or not, which we do often.
这东西是被设定在物体上还是它还在开始。
Is this thing been set on object or
is it still onset.
好吧对我来说这绝对是合理的
All right, for me,
that's a perfectly reasonable
把布尔胁迫放在我的身体里
in placing Boolean coercion
that I'm okay with.
我不喜欢强迫强迫人
I don't like to impose the coerce and
空应变为 false ，而不为 true 。
empty strain the false and
not empty strain the true.
我不喜欢把强迫数字强加给真实或虚假的
I don't like to impose the coerce
numbers to true or false but
我很高兴要么是说要么是要么没有定义
I am perfectly happy with either
saying it's no or undefined,
意思是它没有说，那是错的，或者它被设定在一个物体上。
meaning it's unsaid, and that's falsely or
it's been set to something like an object.
然后就很棘手了我要把所有地方都用在这里
And then it's tricky and
I use that all the all over the place.
所以在我看来我觉得还行，
So in my particular opinion,
I think it's okay,
在我们具体讨论的时候用隐含的方式
to use the implicit to Boolean coercion
when we're specifically talking about
未定义该决策的对象或空。
either an object or
null undefined that decision making.
但是数字和字符串，因为他们有那么多的角落案件，
But the numbers and the strings,
since they have so many corner cases,
我不认为这种含蓄的胁迫会携带自己的重量。
I don't think that that implicit
coercion carries its own weight.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不太想在这里指令性如何
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I'm less trying to be
prescriptive here about exactly how you
应该这样做，更想让你像 JavaScript一样思考。
should do it, and more trying to
get you to think like JavaScript.
让你自己决定我在哪里画这些台词
And make your own determinations for
where do I draw these lines.